adultwhoswho.com 2007-12-16

# Adult Who's Who - Privacy

At adultwhoswho.com (AWW), we are committed to respecting people's privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our website. In order to do so, we may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

**Information submitted by you for inclusion in the AWW directory.**

Information and pictures you provide for inclusion in our directory will be posted on the site, subject to our Terms and Conditions of Use. Such information and pictures will be accessible by all AWW visitors, and AWW has no control over, and shall incur no responsibility for, how such visitors will use such information or pictures. AWW reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such information or pictures, but does not regularly review posted information or pictures. If your information was posted in error, or is incorrect in any way, please contact our information manager for correction or removal. 

**What information does AWW collect?**

When you visit the AWW site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.

In addition to the information we collect upon your initial registration with AWW, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you enter promotions or contests, and when you respond to a survey.

**What do we do with the information we collect?**

1\. It is used to fulfill and maintain your profile registration.

2\. Your phone number may be used in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you and cannot reach you by email. 

3\. The e-mail address members supply us with is never sold to any other website owner or merchant. We hate junk mail as much as you. This is why we will only send you e-mail about items that we feel you should know about. This includes special promotional items that AWW personally endorses, membership changes, terms and conditions changes, Holiday cards, and the latest happenings on AWW. If you would like not to be notified by e-mail or would like to change your e-mail address, please send us a note with the customer service form and let us know how we can best serve you.

**With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?**

AWW does not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifying information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If we intend to share such information, you will be notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest. 

**What information do parties other than AWW collect?**

Some advertisers or entities that have links on our site (including as part of the AWW directory) may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. AWW does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

**What are cookies and how do we use them?**

Our site may use cookies to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored content. We also use cookies to remember information you gave us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the site. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, cookies also help us see which areas are popular and which are not. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our sponsors and advertisers. Some advertisers or websites that have links on our site may also use their own cookies. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. You will not be able to log in to AWW if you turn off the cookies option.

**Your consent**

By using the AWW site, you consent to the collection and use of your information by AWW as described in this policy, and you signify your agreement to the AWW Privacy Policy. 

**Cooperation with law enforcement**

AWW fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to release information about members who we believe are in violation of applicable laws or regulations. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically.
